# Selena Li

Chapel Hill, NC 27514 | 252-626-6452 | selenali@live.unc.edu | LinkedIn

# **Objective**

Self-driven and detail-oriented individual interested in building professional experience through computer science related opportunities. Currently have a solid foundation of several programming languages and can apply prior experiences to pick up new skills and troubleshoot problems.

## **EDUCATION**

#### UNIVERSITY OF NORTH CAROLINA AT CHAPEL HILL (AUGUST 2018 - MAY 2022)

- · **Major**: Computer Science
- **Minor**: Statistics and Analytics
- **GPA**: 3.483

# **SKILLS & ABILITIES**

- · Programming Languages:
  - o Proficient in JavaScript, Java, and R.
  - o Familiar with Python
- · UX/UI Frameworks
  - Comfortable with React, jQuery, Bootstraps, and Bulma

- Coursework: Web Programming, Databases,
  Data Structures, Data Science, Discrete
  Structures, Programming Language Concepts
- · Skills
  - o HTML/CSS, SQL, Rest APIs, Git, and OOP
  - Have experience with Adobe Creative Suite and Figma

# ACADEMIC AND PERSONAL PROJECTS

- **PawMates:** Utilized PetFinder API to create tinder-like web application matching adoptable pets to potential owners (React / Firebase / Bootstrap)
- **Twitter-Clone**: News feed web application allowing users to display, manage, and like tweets through AJAX and JSON request to classroom RESTful back-end API server (Class Project)
- · Recreated classic games 2048, Reversi, Connect 4, and Tic Tac Toe using JQUERY.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# Front End Developer Intern | RoleModel Enterprises | September 2020 - October 2020

- · Weekly collaboration with design and frontend team to plan and implement site design
- · Utilized modern web-design practices to revamp site layout and functionality

## **INTEREST & ACTIVITIES**

# Project Lead | UNC Web Dev Club | (2020 - Present)

- Designed website framework for Carolina Homelessness using Adobe XD to present to client (UX/UI)
- · Utilized JS and CSS Frameworks to build website (Bootstrap and React)

#### FILM COMMITTEE | CUAB (CAROLINA UNION ACTIVITIES BOARD) | (2018 - 2020)

· Worked with internal committee and UNC organizations to organize weekly events for student body.

# Summer Externship | AT&T | June - July 2020

• Engaged in professional and personal development through designated AT&T technical courses.